roses.ru 2011-06-04

# FAQ related to security and privacy.

* * *

Our fundamental privacy principle

The information that you supply to the Russian Florists' Network is considered confidential and will not be shared with others. 

Privacy FAQ

Is my order information private?

The information you provide us regarding yourself is considered private information and will not be shared with others. This includes your name, address, phone, e-mail address, and credit card information. The name and address of the gift recipient, and the card message is shared with the local filling florist, but with no one else. A copy of your order is NOT stored on our web server. 

What are cookies and how does Russian Florists' Network use them?

A cookie is a small file that can be stored on your computer's hard drive. Russian Florists' Network uses cookies to determine the referring site. The cookie does not contain any information about you. If you reject cookies, you can still use our site to order flowers. 

What is an IP address and how does Russian Florists' Network use them?

An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you are using your browser on the Internet. The servers that run our web site identify your computer by its IP address. We do log IP addresses, but the addresses are not linked to individual customer orders nor are they used in any other way to personally identify our customers. 

Does Russian Florists' Network ensure the privacy practices of other sites to which it provides links?

The Russian Florists' Network contains links to other Web sites. Please be aware that our privacy policy does not apply to these linked sites. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement when interacting with any Web site. 

Are there any circumstances where you would share my private information?

In rare circumstances the private information you provide the Russian Florists' Network may be shared with appropriate law enforcement or investigative authorities if we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to; (1) comply with the law, (2) stop credit card fraud; (3) protect against misuse of our website; or (4) protect the personal safety of our site users or the public. The purpose of this disclosure would be to identify, contact or bring legal action against anyone who may attempt to cause injury to another's rights or property. 

How secure is my Russian Florists' Network information?

When you place an order, you are given the option of using our Secure Order Form. By choosing the secure form, you establish a secure connection between your computer and our server using Secure Sockets Layers (SSL), an advanced encryption technology used to protect the storage and transfer of your data from unauthorized parties. Your order remains encrypted until it is safely behind the firewall of our order-processing center. A copy of your order is NOT stored on our web server. 

Is my credit card information stored on your server?

In order to increase the security of your shopping we DO NOT store your credit card information on our server. The credit card processing is being done on higlhly secure server of our credit card processing company. 

How will I know when Russian Florists' Network changes its privacy policy?

If we decide to change the privacy policy for Russian Florists' Network, we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. 

How can I contact Russian Florists' Network if I have concerns regarding my privacy?

If you have questions at any time regarding our privacy policy, you may contact Russian Florists' Network by sending a note to [info@roses.ru](mailto:info@roses.ru) or to the following address: 

Russian Florists' Network  
50 Peterburgskaja str  
Kazan Russia 420107
